const data1 = [
  {
      "category": "SPORTS",
      "questions": [
      { 
          "question": "The Urawa Reds plays this sport",
          "answer": "Soccer",
          "points": 100,
          "difficulty": 1,                     
      },
    {
          
          "question": "This is a Japanese sport. You use bamboo swords to hit your opponent.",
          "answer": "Kendo",
          "points": 200,
          "difficulty": 1,                     
      },
      {
          
          "question": "This sport is played in a pool.",
          "answer": "Swimming",
          "points": 300,
          "difficulty": 1,                     
      },
      {
          
          "question": "This sport is played by firing arrows at a target.",
          "answer": "Archery",
          "points": 400,
          "difficulty": 1,                     
      },
      {
          
          "question": "This sport is played by hitting a small ball into a hole.",
          "answer": "Golf",
          "points": 500,
          "difficulty": 1,                     
      }
  ]
  }
 ,
  {
      "category": "AT SCHOOL",
      "questions": [
          {
              "question": "This is what the teachers write on in the classroom.",
              "answer": "Blackboard",
              "points": 100,
              "difficulty": 1,                     
          },
          {   
              "question": "This room has many books. You can go there to study.",
              "answer": "Library",
              "points": 200,
              "difficulty": 1,                     
          },
          {              
              "question": "This is where you go to buy food.",
              "answer": "Cafeteria",
              "points": 300,
              "difficulty": 1,                     
          },
          {               
              "question": "This is where you go to play sports outdoors.",
              "answer": "Field/Grounds",
              "points": 400,
              "difficulty": 1,                     
          },
          {          
              "question": "This is where you go to play sports indoors and have ceremonies. ",
              "answer": "Gymnasium",
              "points": 500,
              "difficulty": 1,                     
          }
      ]
  }
    ,
    {
      "category": "SCHOOL SUBJECTS",
      "questions": [
          {         
              "question": "You learn how to do calculations in this subject.",
              "answer": "Math",               
              "points": 100,
              "difficulty": 1,                     
          },
          {
              
              "question": "You learn about and play sports in this subject.",
              "answer": "Physical Education",
              "points": 200,
              "difficulty": 1,                     
          },
          {
              
              "question": "You learn about the past in this subject.",
              "answer": "History",
              "points": 300,
              "difficulty": 1,                     
          },
          {
              
              "question": "You learn about the human body and other living things in this subject.",
              "answer": "Biology",
              "points": 400,
              "difficulty": 1,                     
          },
          {
              
              "question": "You learn about maps in this subject.",
              "answer": "Geography",
              "points": 500,
              "difficulty": 1,                     
          }
      ]
    }
  ,
    {
      "category": "JOBS",
      "questions": [
          {
        
              "question": "This person helps students to learn.",
              "answer": "Teacher",
              "points": 100,
              "difficulty": 1,                     
          },
          {
              
              "question": "This person makes food.",
              "answer": "Cook/Chef",
              "points": 200,
              "difficulty": 1,                     
          },
          {
              
              "question": "This person performs in movies.",
              "answer": "Actor/Actress",
              "points": 300,
              "difficulty": 1,                     
          },
          {
              
              "question": "This person is a doctor for animals.",
              "answer": "Veterinarian",
              "points": 400,
              "difficulty": 1,                     
          },
          {
              
              "question": "This person fixes cars.",
              "answer": "Mechanic",
              "points": 500,
              "difficulty": 1,                     
          }
      ]
    }
  
  ,
    {
      "category": "FOOD",
      "questions": [
          {        
              "question": "This is a fruit. It is long and yellow. It tastes sweet.",
              "answer": "Banana",
              "points": 100,
              "difficulty": 1,                     
          },
          {    
              "question": "The meat comes from cows.",
              "answer": "Beef",
              "points": 200,
              "difficulty": 1,                     
          },
          {           
              "question": "This is a popular food for Japanese people around Christmas time.",
              "answer": "Fried Chicken/KFC",
              "points": 300,
              "difficulty": 1,                     
          },
          {              
              "question": "This is a popular breakfast food. They are white or brown. You crack it to cook it.",
              "answer": "Egg",
              "points": 400,
              "difficulty": 1,                     
          },
          {           
              "question": "It is usually made of meat in between two buns. You can buy it at McDonald's.",
              "answer": "Hamburger",
              "points": 500,
              "difficulty": 1,                     
          },
      ]
    } 
];

export default data1;